Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 6 and District 6 Locals, 1936-1995 UE.4.1.6
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 6 Locals, 2.
  - Local 646
    - Local 646 Crown Creative Correspondence, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Local 646 Crown Creative Pension, 1979 - 1982 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Local 646 Crown Creative Industries Strike Correspondence, 1974 - 1979 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Local 647
    - Local 647 Correspondence Regarding Constitution, 1989 - 1994 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Local 651
      - Local 651 Member List, Armstrong Fixtures, 1989 - 1992 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Local 651 Armstrong Store Fixture Corporation Contracts, 1990 - 1993 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Local 651 Armstrong Affiliation Records, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - Local 651 Affiliation Information, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Local 651 Affiliation Ballots, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - Local 651 Record of Affiliation, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - Local 651 Correspondence Regarding Constitution, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Local 651 Miscellaneous, 1976 - 1991 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Local 650
    - Local 650 Custom Concepts, 1968 - 1992 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Local 650 Custom Concepts Pension Plan, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Local 650 Formation and Dissolution, 1986 - 1992 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Local 650 Custom Concepts Pension Material, 1986 - 1987 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Local 650 Custom Concepts Agreement, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Local 650 Custom Concepts Correspondence, 1987 - 1988 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Local 650 Correspondence Regarding Constitution, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Local 689
    - Local 689 Bruce Plastic Strike Correspondence, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Local 699
    - Local 699 Pennzoil Products Company Charter and Constitution, 1994 - 1995 (Box 13, Folder 31)